[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Melman the Giraffe in love with in the 2008 animated comedy movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "Gloria", "incorrect_answers": ["Alex", "Himself", "A female veterinarian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous supermodel did Leonardo DiCaprio date from from 2001 to 2005?", "correct_answer": "Gisele B\u00fcndchen", "incorrect_answers": ["Naomi Campbell", "Heidi Klum", "Tyra Banks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1924, Raymond Dart discovered a fossil which he called Australopithecanthropus africanis.  What is the meaning of the name?", "correct_answer": "The ape man from southern Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "The old man from Australia", "The man from the Mesolithic Age"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no country in the world whose name begins with this letter of the alphabet.", "correct_answer": "X", "incorrect_answers": ["O", "Q", "Y"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Great Escape, Charles Bronson played Lt. David Vilinski, known as the Mole.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most lions only survive in Africa. But a population of the much endangered Asiatic lion lives in India. How many estimated lions live in India as of 2007?", "correct_answer": "300", "incorrect_answers": ["550", "1,500", "3,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the tallest waterfall made by humans, which is located in Umbria, Italy?", "correct_answer": "Cascata delle Marmore", "incorrect_answers": ["Cascata del Maria", "Cascata del Mare", "Cascata delle Maccheroni"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The popular female names Alice, Alicia and Alisha, all mean what?", "correct_answer": "Nobility", "incorrect_answers": ["Spite", "Whole", "Incarnation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetables are used for the preparation of the traditional Spanish stew Fabada Asturiana?", "correct_answer": "Beans", "incorrect_answers": ["Leek", "Eggplants", "Carrots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where would you find the shortest river in the world?", "correct_answer": "Montana", "incorrect_answers": ["Wales", "Ecuador", "Tasmania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Widely known as Crazy Bet, she was a famous Union spy in the American Civil War.", "correct_answer": "Elizabeth Van Lew", "incorrect_answers": ["Betty Carson", "Elizabeth Jenkins", "Elizabeth Garrison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following states has an official motto In God we trust, which is also the official motto of the United States of America?", "correct_answer": "Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgia", "Washington", "South Dakota"]}]